competoid.com 2018-12-17

# About us - Competoid.com

This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for users registering accounts after that date.

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of our websites, emails, and mobile applications ("Site"). The terms "we", "us", and "Team competoid" refer to competoid.com. When you use the Site, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

User agrees and undertakes to use the Website only to ask questions and involve in discussion that is proper. You agree and undertake that when using the Website, you will not:

  * Post any information, data, text, or images, or other material that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, vulgar, obscene, or otherwise objectionable that may invade another's right of privacy or publicity;
  * Post any Material that you do not have a right to reproduce. If you publish other authors work, you must have a written permission of the author of that material.
  * Delete any author attributions, legal notices or proprietary designations or labels that you upload to any communication feature;
  * Upload any material copyright, trademark, patent, or proprietary rights of any third party.
  * Post any material, which can harm our visitors or authors.
  * Use our author's or members emails (published on their request in their profile) to send junk mail, Spam, or chain letters or without their permission.
  * Violate any applicable local, state, national or international law.
  * Post any information or images on discussion forums that may harm any body by any means or unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, vulgar, obscene, or otherwise objectionable that may invade another's right of privacy or publicity
  * Post any messages offensive to other members of this site

## 1\. Information We Collect and How We Use It

When you visit or use our Service, we may store the information you submit to or through the Site, as well as information we collect in connection with your use of the Site.

Among the information we collect, please note:

**1\. Account Information:** If you create an account on Competoid, your full name, email address, zip code and other information such as your gender and birth date may be stored with us that you may provide with your account. You can modify some of the information associated with your account here.

**2\. Content:** The information that you post to the Site is intended for public consumption, including your questions asked, comment on the questions, discussion and account profile. We may display this information on the Site, share it with businesses, and further distribute it to a wider audience through third party sites and services.

**3\. Search:** The search terms you have looked up and results you selected; how long you visited our Service and which features you used

**4\. Communications:** When you sign up for an account, you are opting in to receive emails from Competoid. If you exchange messages with others through the Site, we may store them in order to process and deliver them, allow you to manage them, and investigate possible wrong doing in connection with the Site.

**5\. Site Activity:** We may store information about your use of the Site, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Site, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, location, and requested and referring URLs.

## 2\. Cookies

We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called "flash cookies"), and similar technology in connection with your use of the Site and third party websites ("Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Site, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session.

## 3\. Intellectual Property Rights

www.competoid.com web portal includes contents/material which are intellectual property right of Competoid and User in no event shall acquire any right, title or interest in the same.

User undertakes not to make commercial and/or unauthorized use of the content/material by means of publication, transmission, performance, distribution, caching, printing hard copies for distribution and selling or otherwise gained from the web portal. The content/material on web portal is for personal use only. Competoid reserves the right to remove/discard any infringing copyrighted/other Intellectual property right material/content by Users

## 4\. Third Parties

We may share information about you with third parties as follows:

**1\. Aggregate Information:** We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertisements.

**2\. Links:** The Site may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

**3\. Email address:** This information helps you create an Competoid account. We use this information to help you getting reports to your email address.

## 5\. Content

Competoid does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any content, nor its merchantability or fitness for any particular. In many instances, the content available through this Website represents the opinions and judgements of the respective information provider, User, or other users not under contract with Competoid. Competoid neither endorses nor is responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement made on the Website by anyone other than authorized Competoid employee / spokespersons while acting in official capacities.

Under no circumstances will Competoid be liable for any loss or damage caused by User's reliance on information obtained through the Website. It is the responsibility of User to evaluate the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information, opinion, advice etc. or other content available through the Website.

Unless you have executed a written agreement with Competoid expressly permitting you to do so, you may not provide a hyperlink to the Website from any other website. Competoid reserves the right to revoke its consent to any link at any time in its sole discretion.

## 6\. Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## 7\. Termination

Competoid at its discretion may terminate the license of the User to use its web portal without notice and to remove/discard any material/content on the web portal. We reserves the right to change, modify, alter, add or delete provision(s) of the terms and conditions including privacy policy and the updating of such terms and conditions/ privacy policy on the website shall be deemed to be a notice to the Users. Users are asked to view the terms and conditions every time they visit.

We shall be relieved of its obligation(s) to the extent that fulfilment of such obligation(s) shall be prevented by or delayed by circumstances beyond the reasonable control including, but not limited to, acts of God, IT/Cyber crime, governmental actions, acts of terrorism, protests, riots, war or national emergency, fire, explosion, flood, epidemic, lock outs, embargo, strikes or other labour disputes, or restraints or delays affecting carrier or inability or delay in obtaining supplies of adequate or suitable materials, hacker attacking, intrusion or attack of computer virus, temporary closure due to government regulation or otherwise.

## 8\. Dispute Resolution

This policy and all questions of its interpretation shall be construed in accordance with the laws of India. Any dispute or difference between us and yourself arising out of or relating to the existence, validity, interpretation, performance or termination of, or otherwise in connection with these terms and conditions ("Dispute"), shall at first instance be attempted to be amicably settled between the parties through good faith negotiations. Either party shall be entitled to invoke such negotiations by giving to the other party a notice to that effect ("Dispute Notice"). If a Dispute is not resolved by way of good faith negotiations within a period of Fort five (45) days from the date when the Dispute Notice was received by the receiving party then either party shall be entitled to refer the Dispute to Arbitration and the provisions of the Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996, as amended ("Arbitration Act"), will apply to such arbitration. Such Arbitration proceedings shall be conducted in Chennai and the courts in Chennai shall have exclusive jurisdiction to entertain any dispute arising out of this policy. The arbitration proceedings shall be conducted in English language.

If you believe that Competoid has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may contact us online by clicking here. or write to us at the following address:

Competoid  
No 1, Sathyamoorthy Street,  
New Perungalathur,  
Chennai  
Tamil Nadu, India  
PIN-600 063  
contact-us@competoid.com

The information we obtain from or about you may be processed and stored in India and our other various servers located across the globe. Each location may provide for different data protection rules than the country in which you reside. If you have any questions relating to your personal data, please write to us on contact-us@competoid.com

## 9\. Modifications to This Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on the Site prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use the Site after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
